<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <image>
     <url>https://nima.ninja/assets/ninja1.png</url>
     <title>Diaries of a Modern Ninja!</title>
     <link>https://nima.ninja/</link>
    </image>
    <title>Diaries of a Modern Ninja!</title>
    <description>Nima&apos;s Diaries!</description>
    <link></link>
    <atom:link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <author>
      <name>Nima</name>
      <email>csh4rk0x00@ProtonMail.com</email>
      <uri>https://csh4rk.github.io/</uri>
    </author>
    
      <item>
        <title>Think and Grow Rich</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Think-Grow-Rich-Publication-Foundation-ebook/dp/B07P896HSJ/ref=sr_1_1?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=think+%26+grow+rich+original&amp;amp;qid=1632985183&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/thinkandgrowrich_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-napoleon-hill&quot;&gt;Author: Napoleon Hill&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-personal-success-classic&quot;&gt;Category: Personal Success Classic&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Think and Grow Rich - Over 80 Million Copies Sold&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This edition of Napoleon Hill’s classic Think and Grow Rich is a reproduction of Napoleon Hill’s personal copy of the first edition, the ONLY original version recommended by The Napoleon Hill Foundation, originally printed in March of 1937.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The most famous of all teachers of success spent “a fortune and the better part of a lifetime of effort” to produce the “Law of Success” philosophy that forms the basis of his books and that is so powerfully summarized and explained for the general public in this book.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Think and Grow Rich, Hill draws on stories of Andrew Carnegie, Thomas Edison, Henry Ford, and other millionaires of his generation to illustrate his principles. This book will teach you the secrets that could bring you a fortune. It will show you not only what to do but how to do it. Once you learn and apply the simple, basic techniques revealed here, you will have mastered the secret of true and lasting success.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Money and material things are essential for freedom of body and mind, but there are some who will feel that the greatest of all riches can be evaluated only in terms of lasting friendships, loving family relationships, understanding between business associates, and introspective harmony which brings one true peace of mind! All who read, understand, and apply this philosophy will be better prepared to attract and enjoy these spiritual values.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;BE PREPARED! When you expose yourself to the influence of this philosophy, you may experience a CHANGED LIFE which can help you negotiate your way through life with harmony and understanding and prepare you for the accumulation of abundant material riches.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Probably the most well-known book on success and definitely one of the best! It was a source of inspiration for many other authors and books…&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//ThinkAndGrowRich</link>
        <link href="/ThinkAndGrowRich"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/ThinkAndGrowRich</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sandworm_A New Era of Cyberwar and the Hunt for the Kremlin&apos;s Most Dangerous Hackers</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Sandworm-Cyberwar-Kremlins-Dangerous-Hackers-ebook/dp/B07GD4MFW2&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/sandworm_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-andy-greenberg&quot;&gt;Author: Andy Greenberg&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-misc-cybersecurity-book&quot;&gt;Category: Misc. Cybersecurity Book&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The true story of the most devastating cyberattack in history and the desperate hunt to identify and track the elite Russian agents behind it, from Wired senior writer Andy Greenberg.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Lays out in chilling detail how future wars will be waged in cyberspace and makes the case that we have done little, as of yet, to prevent it.” —Washington Post&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In 2014, the world witnessed the start of a mysterious series of cyberattacks. Targeting American utility companies, NATO, and electric grids in Eastern Europe, the strikes grew ever more brazen. They culminated in the summer of 2017, when the malware known as NotPetya was unleashed, penetrating, disrupting, and paralyzing some of the world’s largest businesses—from drug manufacturers to software developers to shipping companies. At the attack’s epicenter in Ukraine, ATMs froze. The railway and postal systems shut down. Hospitals went dark. NotPetya spread around the world, inflicting an unprecedented ten billion dollars in damage—the largest, most destructive cyberattack the world had ever seen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The hackers behind these attacks are quickly gaining a reputation as the most dangerous team of cyberwarriors in history: a group known as Sandworm. Working in the service of Russia’s military intelligence agency, they represent a persistent, highly skilled force, one whose talents are matched by their willingness to launch broad, unrestrained attacks on the most critical infrastructure of their adversaries. They target government and private sector, military and civilians alike.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A chilling, globe-spanning detective story, Sandworm considers the danger this force poses to our national security and stability. As the Kremlin’s role in foreign government manipulation comes into greater focus, Sandworm exposes the realities not just of Russia’s global digital offensive, but of an era where warfare ceases to be waged on the battlefield. It reveals how the lines between digital and physical conflict, between wartime and peacetime, have begun to blur—with world-shaking implications.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book was very fun to read. It is a non-technical story that shows how important and dangerous, Industrial Control Systems and Critical Infrastructure can be and how some sophisticated cyber groups and APTs work and how advanced they are.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//Sandworm</link>
        <link href="/Sandworm"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Sandworm</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Limitless_Upgrade Your Brain, Learn Anything Faster, and Unlock Your Exceptional Life</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Limitless-Upgrade-Anything-Faster-Exceptional-ebook/dp/B082ZQDH63/ref=sr_1_1?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=limitless&amp;amp;qid=1632985085&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/limitless_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-jim-kwik&quot;&gt;Author: Jim Kwik&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-personal-transformation&quot;&gt;Category: Personal Transformation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;JIM KWIK, the world’s #1 brain coach, has written the owner’s manual for mental expansion and brain fitness. Limitless gives people the ability to accomplish more, more productivity, more transformation, more personal success, and business achievement, by changing their Mindset, Motivation, and Methods.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These “3 M’s” live in the pages of Limitless along with practical techniques that unlock the superpowers of your brain and change your habits.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For over 25 years, Jim Kwik has worked closely with successful men and women who are at the top in their fields as actors, athletes, CEOs, and business leaders from all walks of life, to unlock their true potential. In this groundbreaking book, he reveals the science-based practices and field-tested tips to accelerate self-learning, communication, memory, focus, recall, and speed reading, to create fast, hard results.
 Learn how to:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;HARNESS YOUR MINDSET
Your brain is like a supercomputer, and your thoughts program it to run. That’s why the Kwik Brain process starts with unmasking assumptions, habits, and procrastinations that stifle you, redrawing the borders and boundaries of what you think is possible. It teaches you how to identify what you want in every aspect of your life so that you can move from negative thinking to positive possibilities.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;IGNITE YOUR MOTIVATION
Uncovering what motivates you is the key that opens up limitless mental capacity. This is where Passion + Purpose + Energy meet to move you closer to your goals while staying focused and clear. Your personal excitement will be sustainable with self-renewing inspirations. Your mind starts strong, stays healthy, and drives further exponentially faster.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;MASTER THE METHODS
We’ve applied the latest neuroscience for accelerated learning. Our process, programs, podcasts, and products unleash your brain’s own superpowers. Finish a book 3x faster through speed reading (and remember every part of it), learn a new language in record time, and master new skills with ease. These are just a few of the life-changing, self-help benefits. With Kwik Brain, you’ll get brain-fit and level-up your mental performance.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With the best Mindset, Motivation, and Method, your powers become truly limitless.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Jim Kwik is a very good mentor, he teaches the latest and most effective methods on memory improvement, better learning, speed reading and overall personal transformation. I really learned a lot from this book. He knows what he’s talking about and he’s lived it.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//Limitsless</link>
        <link href="/Limitsless"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Limitsless</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flow_The Psychology of Optimal Experience</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Flow-Psychology-Experience-Perennial-Classics-ebook/dp/B000W94FE6/ref=sr_1_1?crid=3S0FE0VDE81LY&amp;amp;dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=flow+the+psychology+of+optimal+experience&amp;amp;qid=1632985238&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;sprefix=flow%2Cdigital-text%2C735&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/flow_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-mihaly-csikszentmihalyi&quot;&gt;Author: Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-psychology-of-creativity--genius&quot;&gt;Category: Psychology of Creativity &amp;amp; Genius&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“Explores a happy state of mind called flow, the feeling of complete engagement in a creative or playful activity.” — Time&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The bestselling classic that holds the key to unlocking meaning, creativity, peak performance, and true happiness.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Legendary psychologist Mihaly Csikszentmihalyi’s famous investigations of “optimal experience” have revealed that what makes an experience genuinely satisfying is a state of consciousness called flow. During flow, people typically experience deep enjoyment, creativity, and a total involvement with life. In this new edition of his groundbreaking classic work, Csikszentmihalyi (“the leading researcher into ‘flow states’” —Newsweek) demonstrates the ways this positive state can be controlled, not just left to chance. Flow: The Psychology of Optimal Experience teaches how, by ordering the information that enters our consciousness, we can discover true happiness, unlock our potential, and greatly improve the quality of our lives.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book describes a human conscious state known as Flow. In this state, we feel most joyful, creative, focused, tireless and almost invincible.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people have experienced this state some times in their life but can’t pinpoint exactly what it was or how to repeat and experience it again.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This book is all about Flow, how to create and sustain it so we can have more joyful and meaningful moments in our life and work.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//Flow</link>
        <link href="/Flow"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Flow</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Essentialism_The Disciplined Pursuit of Less</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Essentialism-Disciplined-Pursuit-Greg-McKeown-ebook/dp/B00G1J1D28/ref=sr_1_1?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=essentialism&amp;amp;qid=1632985276&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/essentialism_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-greg-mckeown&quot;&gt;Author: Greg Mckeown&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-business-decision-making&quot;&gt;Category: Business Decision-Making&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER • More than one million copies sold! Essentialism isn’t about getting more done in less time. It’s about getting only the right things done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“A timely, essential read for anyone who feels overcommitted, overloaded, or overworked.”—Adam Grant&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have you ever:
• found yourself stretched too thin?
• simultaneously felt overworked and underutilized?
• felt busy but not productive?
• felt like your time is constantly being hijacked by other people’s agendas?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you answered yes to any of these, the way out is the Way of the Essentialist.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentialism is more than a time-management strategy or a productivity technique. It is a systematic discipline for discerning what is absolutely essential, then eliminating everything that is not, so we can make the highest possible contribution toward the things that really matter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;By forcing us to apply more selective criteria for what is Essential, the disciplined pursuit of less empowers us to reclaim control of our own choices about where to spend our precious time and energy—instead of giving others the implicit permission to choose for us.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Essentialism is not one more thing—it’s a whole new way of doing everything. It’s about doing less, but better, in every area of our lives. Essentialism is a movement whose time has come.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This books shows the power and importance of essentialism and removing distractions and trivial things to focus all of our energy on our primary and most important goals in life.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//Essentialism</link>
        <link href="/Essentialism"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/Essentialism</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Deep Work_Rules for Focused Success in a Distracted World</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Deep-Work-Focused-Success-Distracted-ebook/dp/B00X47ZVXM/ref=sr_1_1?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=deep+work&amp;amp;qid=1632985269&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/deepwork_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-cal-newport&quot;&gt;Author: Cal Newport&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-time-management--career-guide&quot;&gt;Category: Time Management / Career Guide&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Master one of our economy’s most rare skills and achieve groundbreaking results with this “exciting” book (Daniel H. Pink) from an “exceptional” author (New York Times Book Review).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Deep work is the ability to focus without distraction on a cognitively demanding task. It’s a skill that allows you to quickly master complicated information and produce better results in less time. Deep Work will make you better at what you do and provide the sense of true fulfillment that comes from craftsmanship. In short, deep work is like a super power in our increasingly competitive twenty-first century economy. And yet, most people have lost the ability to go deep-spending their days instead in a frantic blur of e-mail and social media, not even realizing there’s a better way.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In Deep Work, author and professor Cal Newport flips the narrative on impact in a connected age. Instead of arguing distraction is bad, he instead celebrates the power of its opposite. Dividing this book into two parts, he first makes the case that in almost any profession, cultivating a deep work ethic will produce massive benefits. He then presents a rigorous training regimen, presented as a series of four “rules,” for transforming your mind and habits to support this skill.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Work Deeply&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Embrace Boredom&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Quit Social Media&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drain the Shallows&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A mix of cultural criticism and actionable advice, Deep Work takes the reader on a journey through memorable stories-from Carl Jung building a stone tower in the woods to focus his mind, to a social media pioneer buying a round-trip business class ticket to Tokyo to write a book free from distraction in the air-and no-nonsense advice, such as the claim that most serious professionals should quit social media and that you should practice being bored. Deep Work is an indispensable guide to anyone seeking focused success in a distracted world.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;An Amazon Best Book of 2016 Pick in Business &amp;amp; Leadership
Wall Street Journal Business Bestseller
A Business Book of the Week at 800-CEO-READ&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is also one of the best books that I’ve read. It has very good points on what life distractions are and how to remove them, that’s the only way to have a meaningful life and to lead a career that makes a difference.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//DeepWork</link>
        <link href="/DeepWork"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/DeepWork</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>The Compound Effect_Jumpstart Your Income, Your Life, Your Success</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Compound-Effect-Jumpstart-Income-Success-ebook/dp/B089GM2W99/ref=sr_1_2?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=compund+effect&amp;amp;qid=1632986805&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;sr=1-2&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/compoundeffect_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-darren-hardy&quot;&gt;Author: Darren Hardy&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-personal-transformation&quot;&gt;Category: Personal Transformation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you want success? More success than you have now? And even more success than you ever imagined possible? That is what this book is about. Achieving it.
No gimmicks. No hyperbole. Finally, just the truth on what it takes to earn success
As the central curator of the success media industry for over 25 years, author Darren Hardy has heard it all, seen it all, and tried most of it. This book reveals the core principles that drive success. The Compound Effect contains the essence of what every super achiever needs to know, practice, and master to obtain extraordinary success. Inside you will find strategies on:
How to win–every time! The No. 1 strategy to achieve any goal and triumph over any competitor, even if they’re smarter, more talented or more experienced.
Eradicating your bad habits (some you might be unaware of!) that are derailing your progress.
Painlessly installing the few key disciplines required for major breakthroughs.
The real, lasting keys to motivation–how to get yourself to do things you don’t feel like doing.
Capturing the elusive, awesome force of momentum. Catch this, and you’ll be unstoppable.
The acceleration secrets of super achievers. Do they have an unfair advantage? Yes, they do, and now you can too!
If you’re serious about living an extraordinary life, use the power of The Compound Effect to create the success you desire. Begin your journey today!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This one was simply the best book that I read last year. This book should be read after &lt;a href=&quot;/AtomicHabits&quot;&gt;Atomic Habits&lt;/a&gt;, they supplement each other.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//CompoundEffect</link>
        <link href="/CompoundEffect"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/CompoundEffect</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Atomic Habits_An Easy &amp; Proven Way to Build Good Habits &amp; Break Bad Ones</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.amazon.com/Atomic-Habits-Proven-Build-Break-ebook/dp/B07D23CFGR/ref=sr_1_1?dchild=1&amp;amp;keywords=atomic+habits&amp;amp;qid=1632985127&amp;amp;s=digital-text&amp;amp;sr=1-1&quot;&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/atomichabits_book.jpg&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;author-james-clear&quot;&gt;Author: James Clear&lt;/h4&gt;
&lt;h4 id=&quot;category-personal-transformation&quot;&gt;Category: Personal Transformation&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The #1 New York Times bestseller. Over 3 million copies sold!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tiny Changes, Remarkable Results&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No matter your goals, Atomic Habits offers a proven framework for improving–every day. James Clear, one of the world’s leading experts on habit formation, reveals practical strategies that will teach you exactly how to form good habits, break bad ones, and master the tiny behaviors that lead to remarkable results.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re having trouble changing your habits, the problem isn’t you. The problem is your system. Bad habits repeat themselves again and again not because you don’t want to change, but because you have the wrong system for change. You do not rise to the level of your goals. You fall to the level of your systems. Here, you’ll get a proven system that can take you to new heights.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Clear is known for his ability to distill complex topics into simple behaviors that can be easily applied to daily life and work. Here, he draws on the most proven ideas from biology, psychology, and neuroscience to create an easy-to-understand guide for making good habits inevitable and bad habits impossible. Along the way, readers will be inspired and entertained with true stories from Olympic gold medalists, award-winning artists, business leaders, life-saving physicians, and star comedians who have used the science of small habits to master their craft and vault to the top of their field.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Learn how to:
  •  make time for new habits (even when life gets crazy);
  •  overcome a lack of motivation and willpower;
  •  design your environment to make success easier;
  •  get back on track when you fall off course;
…and much more.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Atomic Habits will reshape the way you think about progress and success, and give you the tools and strategies you need to transform your habits–whether you are a team looking to win a championship, an organization hoping to redefine an industry, or simply an individual who wishes to quit smoking, lose weight, reduce stress, or achieve any other goal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&quot;my-comment&quot;&gt;My Comment:&lt;/h3&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some books are good, some are exceptional. This one was one of the best books that I read last year.
It is highly recommended. Read it with &lt;a href=&quot;/CompoundEffect&quot;&gt;The Compound Effect&lt;/a&gt; , these two books should be read together.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 30 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//AtomicHabits</link>
        <link href="/AtomicHabits"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/AtomicHabits</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>My first post!</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/panda1.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is my first post!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0330</pubDate>
        <link>//My-First-Post</link>
        <link href="/My-First-Post"/>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/My-First-Post</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
